

PROFILE

0961827236

tamvo0610@gmail.com

O Hoc Mon, Ho Chi Minh City

EDUCATION

2014 - 2018

University of Natural Resources and Environment Ho Chi Minh City

Land Adminstration

SKILLS

Technical:

- HTML5
- CSS3/SCSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- JSX/ES6
- ReactJs
- React Native
- Redux
- Git

Soft Skills:

- English Reading and Writing
- Teamwork

VÕ CHÍ TÂM

Front-End Developer

SUMMARY

I am a motivated and self-learner Front-end Developer with about 2 year's experience in programming.

I am seeking a position with a company that will require me to utilize my skills, abilities, and experience in the IT field to ensure the company's success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

3/2021 - Present

Skydev.vn

- Develop website using HTML, CSS, ReactJS, ...
- Develop mobile app using React Native, ...
- Implemented enhancements that improved app, and web functionality and responsiveness.

Self-Learning

10/2020 - 2/2021

Start learning web developer at https://fullstack.edu.vn

PROJECTS

CafeFinz Website - Mobile App

2022

Description:

- Application of a real estate company, with the function of managing real estate projects.
- The application has functions related to create and manage community groups and users.

Responsibilities:

- Web:
 - o Implement UI from Figma use Antd, less, ...
 - Intergrate API
- App
 - Implement UI from Figma
 - o Set up Stack, protect and navigation between screens
 - Intergrate API
 - o Publish app to TestLight, App Center

AWARDS

Remarkable Employee 2022

INTEREST

- Fooball
- Swimming
- Music

Technologies:

- NextJs for Web
- · React Native for App Mobile

Store:

- https://apps.apple.com/vn/app/cafefinz/id6444694383
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.cafefinz.cafefinzapp

Virtual Event Website

2022

Description:

 A website that can host 360° events, based on Zoom SDK so that user can create or join meetings, with SignalR real-time chatting and playing games features.

Responsibilities:

- Implement UI from Figma use Antd, less, ...
- Intergrate API with axios, react querry, ...

Technologies:

ReactJS

Website: https://ve.dev.skydev.vn

Kuula Website

2022

Description:

 A website that supports creating 360° Virtual Tours for businesses, with tour interation and sharing features.

Responsibilities:

- Implement UI from Figma use Antd, less, ...
- Intergrate API with

Technologies:

ReactJS

Website: https://kuula.dev.skydev.vn

Gotec Land Mobile App

2021

Description:

 Application of a real estate company, with the function of managing real estate projects.

Technologies:

React Native

Responsibilities:

- Implement UI from Figma
- Intergrate API with Axios

Store:

- https://apps.apple.com/vn/app/gotecland/id1595636804
- https://play.google.com/store/apps/details? id=com.gotecland.app